gamesforgame.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy

To protecting your privacy online, Gamesforgame.com have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online.

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you, on a voluntary basis, when you register on our site or send us questions or comments via e-mail. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes, We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. A "cookie" is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer (if you allow). Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Gamesforgame.com use these third parties services (you can check their respective privacy policy  following this links): [Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense), [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/), [Cpmstar](http://www.cpmstar.com/), [Histats](http://www.histats.com/), [Mochimedia](http://www.mochimedia.com/).

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising [opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).)

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Children**

Games For Game does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the website or our services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on this website or our services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Games For Game through this website or our services, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [HERE](http://www.gamesforgame.com/terms-of-use)

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our website Privacy Policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

 **To create link towards this article on your website,  
copy and paste the text below in your page.**

Preview :

To protecting your privacy online, Gamesforgame.com have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information... 

GamesForGame is a free flash games site with frequent game's updates. Moreover this site have a list of downloadables games. The most played categories are: action games, adventure games, dress-up games, driving games, puzzles games and shooting games. With bike games, car rancing and car parking games and Monster Truck games. Moreover this site have: super Mario Bros flash games, Hannah Montana games, ultimate flash Sonic the Hedgehog 3 games and sonic adventure 2 battle game, adrenaline challenge and Power Rangers Dino Thunder game. 

Copyright © 2019 Games For Game. All Rights Reserved. VAT: IT03151450792
